currencio.co 2019-08-07

# Privacy Policy — Currencio

Market Cap: $298 689 266 474

Coins: 1 760 Exchanges: 218 Market Cap: $298 689 266 474 Volume (24h): $60 754 278 112

This Privacy Policy will inform you on:

  * The Website’s Privacy Practices when handling your Personal Data
  * The Website’s Sources on collecting of your Personal Data
  * The Website’s method of processing of your Personal Data

Your personal data is your right. This Privacy Policy will apply in cases where we are acting as a data Controller with respect to the Personal Data of our Users and Website visitors; in other words, where we determine the purposes and means of the processing of that personal data. Our usage of cookies are conditioned on your prior permission. If you have any questions in regards to our Privacy practices, please contact us at: currencio.co/contact/

## Your Personal Data

  1. What Data do we collect? – In order to provide you with our services, we may process certain data in connection to your personal profile (such as: your name, address, telephone number, e-mail address, gender, date of birth, profile picture), data in connection to our services (data we have collected in order to provide you with our services), publication data (we may process information that you post for publication on our Website), enquiry, correspondence and notification data (any data you provide us with in any enquiry you submit to us, for example through our Customer Support e-mail, or by your consent to opt in to subscription for newsletters or promotional e-mails), your transaction data (information in relation to transactions, without exclusion to purchases of goods and services, that include your contact details and transaction details). 
  2. How do we use your Data? – We process your data in accordance to these Terms of Service and Privacy Policy at all times. We do not store or retain data that is connected to your transactions, unless you have authorized us to do otherwise. When appropriate and effective, we may share some of your personal Data with third parties that perform certain services to us – for example, we may share your personal Data with our personal billing, marketing and technology services, or your transaction details with our authorized payment provider. All of these service providers have an established agreement with us and shall process the data in accordance to the best of privacy standards available. All of the data that is relating to your enquiries or financial transactions that are sent from the web browser to our server will be protected by using encryption technology. Personal Data including your name, contact information, cardholder data and possible stored passwords will always be stored in encrypted form. 
  3. How long do we retain your Data? – Personal data that we process for any purpose or purposes shall not be kept for longer than is necessary for that purpose or those purposes. We will retain your personal data for a minimum period of 1 years following registration time, and for a maximum period of 2 years following registration time. In some cases, namely when it is not possible for us to specify in advance the periods for which your personal data will be retained. In such cases, we will determine the period of retention based on the period of retention of personal data as determined on our behalf. We may retain your personal data where such retention is necessary for compliance with a legal obligation to which we are the subject, or in order to protect your vital interests or the vital interests of another third party. 
  4. Your Data equals your Rights! – Your personal data is your right, and our obligation is to be transparent about the way we may use it for the purposes of providing our services to us. We have compiled a list of your rights that you may exercise at any time. For more information, please send us a question on our Customer Support e-mail, or inform yourself about your rights in-depth by reading the new privacy regulations. You may exercise the rights included below by sending a notice to us at any time:

    1. Right to Access – You have the right to confirmation as to whether or not we process your personal data and, where we do, access to the personal data, together with certain additional information (which includes details of the purpose of processing, categories of personal data concerned and the recipients of the personal data). Where there is no legal constraint, we will supply to you a copy of your personal data. The first copy will be provided free of charge, with the additional copies being subject to a reasonable fee. 
    2. Right to Rectification – You have the right to have any inaccurate personal data about you rectified and, taking into account the purposes of the processing, to have any incomplete personal data about you completed.
    3. Right to Erasure – In certain cases, you have the right to erasure of your personal data without undue delay. Those circumstances include: the personal data are no longer necessary in relation to the purposes for which they were collected or otherwise processed; you withdraw consent to consent-based processing; you object to the processing under certain rules of applicable data protection law; the processing is for direct marketing purposes; and the personal data have been unlawfully processed. However, there are exclusions of the right to erasure. The general exclusions include where processing is necessary: for exercising the right of freedom of expression and information; for compliance with a legal obligation; or for the establishment, exercise or defense of legal claims. 
    4. Right of Processing Restriction – In some circumstances you have the right to restrict the processing of your personal data. Those circumstances are: you contest the accuracy of the personal data; processing is unlawful but you oppose erasure; we no longer need the personal data for the purposes of our processing, but you require personal data for the establishment, exercise or defense of legal claims; and you have objected to processing, pending the verification of that objection. Where processing has been restricted on this basis, we may continue to store your personal data. However, we will only otherwise process it: with your consent; for the establishment, exercise or defense of legal claims; for the protection of the rights of another natural or legal person; or for reasons of important public interest. 
    5. Right to Object Processing – You have the right to object to our processing of your personal data on grounds relating to your particular situation, but only to the extent that the legal basis for the processing is that the processing is necessary for: the performance of a task carried out in the public interest or in the exercise of any official authority vested in us; or the purposes of the legitimate interests pursued by us or by a third party. If you make such an objection, we will cease to process the personal information unless we can demonstrate compelling legitimate grounds for the processing which override your interests, rights and freedoms, or the processing is for the establishment, exercise or defense of legal claims. You have the right to object to our processing of your personal data for direct marketing purposes (including profiling for direct marketing purposes). If you make such an objection, we will cease to process your personal data for this purpose. You have the right to object to our processing of your personal data for scientific or historical research purposes or statistical purposes on grounds relating to your particular situation, unless the processing is necessary for the performance of a task carried out for reasons of public interest. 
    6. Right to Data Portability – To the extent that the legal basis for our processing of your Data is: - consent; - necessary for the performance of a contract to which you are the party, or to take steps at your request prior to entering into contract, and such processing is carried out by automated means, you have the right to receive your personal data from us in a structured, commonly used and machine-readable format, provided that there are no legal restrictions as foreseen by privacy regulations. 
    7. Right to a Complaint to a Supervisory Authority - If you consider that our processing of your personal information infringes data protection laws, you have a legal right to lodge a complaint with a supervisory authority responsible for data protection. You may do so in the EU member state of your habitual residence, your place of work or the place of the alleged infringement. 
    8. Right to Withdraw Consent – In cases in which the legal basis for our processing of your Data is consent, you have the right to withdraw that consent at any time. Withdrawal will not affect the lawfulness of processing before the withdrawal.

## Cookies and Privacy

  1. What are Cookies? – Cookies are small pieces of data that are stored on your static or mobile device’s website browser, or that may be stored locally on your device when you visit our Website. A cookie file contains an identifier, which is a string of letters and numbers that are sent back each time a browser requests a page from the server. Cookies are divided into session cookies (which expire at the end of the user session – i.e. at the time of closure of your device’s website browser), or persistent cookies (which expire at their designated expiry date, unless deleted prior to such date). Cookies do not typically contain any information that personally identifies a user, but personal data that we store about you may be linked to the information stored in and obtained from cookies. 
  2. Why do we use cookies – We may use cookies in order to authenticate you, determine if you are logged into our website, maintain the state of your shopping cart as you navigate through Security Token Network, personalize your user experience when logged in our Security Token Network, to help us display relevant advertisements to you, analyze certain behaviors on our website, store your preferences in relations to the use of cookies, and finally use cookies as an element of security, in order to protect your user account from misuse. 
  3. Your cookie preferences – You can manage your cookie preferences manually, by sending us a request on our Customer Support e-mail at (customer support e-mail). Most browsers that are used by Users allow for User to refuse or accept cookie usage, or to delete the cookies from the browser memory. You can obtain up-to-date information about blocking and deleting cookies on certain browsers on the following links:

Please note that with blocking cookies from your Website browser, or deleting clearing your cookies from your device may limit certain services that we provide – for example: if you delete or block the usage of your authentication cookies, you may have to sign in to your User Account manually every time you visit our Website.

## Our Third-party Services

  1. Currencio may contain links to certain third-party websites and/or similar services. Please note that prior to engaging into any activity with these third-party websites, such websites and services are governed by a separate set of Terms and Conditions and Privacy Policies.
  2. We may use some third-party services in order to help us provide you with an amazing service. Below is a simplified list of our third-party services we may use, alongside the legal basis of processing of your data and their privacy policy:

# | Name of Service and Website | Policies on Privacy | Services used | Purpose for processing | Lawful basis for processing | Type of Data  
---|---|---|---|---|---|---  
1. | Google (Google, Inc. – U.S.) | [Privacy Policy – Opt Out](https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout?hl=en) | Google AdSense, Google AdWords, Google Analytics | Traffic and User behavior information, Advertisement tools | Legitimate interest | Anonymized  

## Contact Us

You may contact us using our Website Contact form at currencio.co/contact/
